Chu Nanfeng,
if you dare to step into this place today,
just try it!
Don't use Wan as an excuse.
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Put your guns down!
Young Master,
you don't need to worry about me.
Let's go back first.
No matter what happened,
let's have a good meal first.
I'm here for you.
Ling Shenxing,
if I remember correctly,
this is our first time eating out alone.
Is this a date?
If you like,
I can take you out every day.
[I never thought I'd meet someone]
[who could make my heart flutter in this novel world.]
[But I don't know if I'll leave here one day.]
[I don't know if this is a blessing]
[or a misfortune.]
[Perhaps all I can do is cherish the moment.]
Take this for self-defense.
Damn it.
The brakes have failed.
Someone must have tampered with the car.
Wan, wake up.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Be careful.
What happened?
I can't move my foot.
I'll help you over there.
Okay.
You must have sprained your ankle
when jumping off the car.
Wait a minute.
Unfasten the belt.
Ah.
What are you thinking?
I don't want a disabled husband.
When I was studying medicine,
I met a man who was like you.
He was seriously injured,
but he kept delaying treatment,
which led to complications
and he died.
Don't be like him.
That man,
didn't anyone care about him?
Of course,
many people cared about him.
But
he always carried everything on his own.
So the Young Marshal
is afraid of pain.
Someone is coming.
Go.
Over there.
Search.
That way.
Go.
They're obviously here to find us.
They may be in league with the saboteur.
They're obviously trying to kill us.
Ling Shenxing is injured.
I have to lure them away.
Ling Shenxing,
do you trust me?
I do.
What are you doing?
Wan.
Ling Shenxing.
I love you.
No matter what the outcome,
I hope you can live well.
[Ling Shenxing always protects me.]
[Although I was injured,]
[this time,]
[it's my turn to protect him.]
[Ling Shenxing,]
[promise me,]
[if I die,]
[you won't marry anyone else.]
Wan.
Come back.
It's me.
Don't be afraid.
I'll always be there for you.
As long as you turn around,
I'll always be there.
In this world,
apart from my family,
no one has ever taken care of me.
I'll take care of you from now on.
Don't worry.
I'll always be there for you.